Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 196504; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Fortune: 7/1974: Edit: Stories: Federal Reserve Board, 197602 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1974: Publishing, 197601 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1975: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197600 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1978: Publishing [empty], 197599 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1975: Harrison House Meeting, Glencove, L.I.: Jan. 24-26, 197598 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1976-1978: Bi-weekly, 197597 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 24-25)
  - Fortune: 1976: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197596 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1976: Publishing, 197595 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1977: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197594 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1977: Publishing, 197593 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1978: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197592 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1979: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197591 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1979: Publishing, 197590 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th: Anthology Issue, 197589 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th: Anthology Issue: Interviews, 197588 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 25th of Fortune 500, 197587 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th, 197586 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197585 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1980: Publishing, 197584 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1981: Publishing, 197583 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197582 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1982: Publishing, 197581 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1983: New format, 197580 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1983: Edit, 197579 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1983: Publishing, 197578 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1984: Edit, 197577 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1984: Publishing, 197576 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1985: Edit, 197575 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1985: Publishing, 197574 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197573 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1986: Letters Reports [empty], 197572 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1986: Publishing, 197571 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1987: Edit, 197570 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1987: Publishing, 197569 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1988: Edit, 197568 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1988: Publishing, 197567 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1989: Edit, 197566 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1989: Publishing, 197565 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1990: Anniversary, 60th: Miscellaneous, 197564 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1990: 60th Anniversary Issue, 197563 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1990: Edit, 197562 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1990: Publishing, 197561 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1991: Edit, 197560 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1991: Publishing, 197559 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1992: Edit, 197558 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1992: Publishing, 197557 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 33)
  - Fortune: 1993: Edit, 197556 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 34)
  - Fortune: 1993: Publishing, 197555 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 35)
  - Fortune: 1994: Edit, 197554 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 36)
  - Fortune: 1994: Publishing, 197553 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 37)
  - Fortune: 1995: Edit, 197552 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 38)
  - Fortune: 1995: Publishing, 197551 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 39)
  - Fortune Book Club, 197550 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 40)
  - Fortune International: 1983 &Before, 197549 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 41)
  - Fortune International: 1983: First Issue, 197548 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 42)
  - Fortune International: 1984, 197547 (Offsite-box 465)
  - Fortune International: 1984 [RESTRICTED], 197546 (Offsite-box R4)
  - FSB: 2002: Edit, 197545 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 44)
  - FYI [employee newsletter], 197544 (Offsite-box 463, Folder 13)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1958-1964, 197543 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 45)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Jan.-Aug., 197542 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 46)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Sept.-Dec., 197541 (Offsite-box 465)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Sept.-Dec. [RESTRICTED], 197540 (Offsite-box R4)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1966, 197539 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 48)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1967-1974, 197537 (Offsite-box 465)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1967-1974 [RESTRICTED], 197536 (Box R4)
  - Golf magazine, 197535 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 51)
  - Growth Markets Group, 197534 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 52)
  - Grupo Editorial Expansion, 197533 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 53)
  - Havers Hills: 1971 & Later, 197532 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 54)
  - Health: Edit, 197531 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 55)
  - Home Box Office: Organization flow chart, 197530 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 56)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Programming, 197529 (Offsite-box 465)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Programming [RESTRICTED], 197528 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Regulatory, 197527 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 58)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Miscellaneous, 197526 (Offsite-box 465)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197525 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Miscellaneous, 197524 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197523 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Personnel & Organization, 197522 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 3)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Programming, 197521 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Programming [RESTRICTED], 197520 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Regulatory, 197519 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Regulatory [RESTRICTED], 197518 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Studio & Network, 197517 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 6)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Personnel & Organization, 197516 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 7)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Programming, 197515 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Programming [RESTRICTED], 197514 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Regulatory, 197513 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 9)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Sales & marketing program guide, 197512 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 10)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Studio & Network, 197511 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 11)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Miscellaneous, 197510 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197509 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Miscellaneous, 197508 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197507 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Programming, 197506 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Programming [RESTRICTED], 197505 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory, 197504 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 17)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory: Satellite, 197503 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory: Satellite [RESTRICTED], 197502 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Satellite: First Launch, 197501 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Satellite: First Launch [RESTRICTED], 197500 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Miscellaneous, 197499 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197498 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Ventures, 197497 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Ventures [RESTRICTED], 197496 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1977: Regulatory, 197495 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 23)
  - Home Box Office: 1977: Miscellaneous, 197494 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 24)
  - Home Box Office: 1978: Showtime: Viacom-Teleprompter join venture, 197493 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 25)
  - Home Box Office: 1978: Miscellaneous, 197492 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 26)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Merrill Lynch video seminar, 197491 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 27)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Miscellaneous, 197490 (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197489 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1980: Miscellaneous, 197488 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 29)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Programming, 197487 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 30)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Regulatory: Premiere, 197486 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 31)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Ventures, 197485 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 32)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Miscellaneous, 197484 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 33)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Tri-Star Pictures, 197483 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 35)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Ventures, 197482 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 36)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Ventures, 197481 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 37)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Miscellaneous, 197480 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 38)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Programming, 197479 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 39)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Programming, 197478 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 40)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Ventures, 197477 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 41)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Miscellaneous, 197476 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 42)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Programming, 197475 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 43)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Ventures, 197474 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 44)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Miscellaneous, 197473 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 45)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Programming, 197472 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 46-47)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Ventures, 197471 (Offsite-box 466, Folder 48)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Miscellaneous, 197470 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 1-2)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Programming, 197469 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 3)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Miscellaneous, 197468 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 4)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Ventures, 197467 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 5)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Programming, 197466 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 6)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Ventures, 197465 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 7)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Video Unit, 197464 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 8)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Miscellaneous, 197463 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 9)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Programming, 197462 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 10)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Ventures, 197461 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 11)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Video Unit, 197460 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 12)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Miscellaneous, 197459 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 13)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Independent productions, 197458 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 14)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Programming, 197457 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 15)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Ventures, 197456 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 16)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Video Unit, 197455 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 17)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Miscellaneous, 197454 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 18)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Enterprises, 197453 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 19)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Independent productions [empty], 197452 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 20)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Miscellaneous, 197451 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 21)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Programming, 197450 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 22)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Ventures, 197449 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 23)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Video Unit, 197448 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 24)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Enterprises [empty], 197447 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 25)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Programming, 197446 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 26)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Miscellaneous, 197445 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 27)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Ventures, 197444 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 28)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Video Unit, 197443 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 29)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Programming, 197442 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 30)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Ventures, 197441 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 31)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Miscellaneous, 197440 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 32)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Programming, 197439 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 33)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Ventures, 197438 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 34)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Miscellaneous, 197437 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 35)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Programming, 197436 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 36)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Miscellaneous, 197435 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 37)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Ventures, 197434 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 38)
  - Information Systems, 197433 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 39)
  - Inland Container Corporation: 1978 & Later, 197432 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 40)
  - In Style: 1994-: Edit, 197431 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 41)
  - In Style: 1994-: Publishing, 197430 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 42)
  - International: Russia, 197429 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 43)
  - International (TLI): 1961-1962, 197428 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 44)
  - International (TLI): 1963-1965, 197427 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 45)
  - International (TLI): 1966-1972, 197426 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 46)
  - International (TLI): 1973 & Later, 197425 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 1)
  - IPC, 197424 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 2)
  - Legal Department: 1961-1978, 197423 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Legal Department: 1961-1978 [RESTRICTED], 197422 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Legal Department: 1979-, 197421 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Legal Department: 1979- [RESTRICTED], 197420 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Letters Magazine, 197419 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Letters Magazine [RESTRICTED], 197418 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life magazine, 197417 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Flavio, 197416 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Flavio [RESTRICTED], 197415 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Astronauts, 197414 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197413 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Civil Defense [empty], 197412 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Comment, 197411 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Fred Schwartz case (1), 197410 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Fred Schwartz case (2), 197409 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Life Society, 197408 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March, 197407 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: April-May, 197406 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-August, 197405 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept.-Dec., 197404 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1961: Anniversary, 25th, 197403 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1961: Publishing, 197402 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (1), 197401 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (1) [RESTRICTED], 197400 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (2), 197399 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (2) [RESTRICTED], 197398 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Comment, 197397 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Supplements &Life Society, 197396 (Offsite-box 468-469)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Tax round table, 197395 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-Feb., 197394 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: March-April, 197393 (Offsite-box 468, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-June, 197392 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Dec., 197391 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1962: Publishing (1), 197390 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1962: Publishing (2), 197389 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Astronauts, 197388 (Offsite-box 469)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197387 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Comment, 197386 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Supplements &Premium Editions &Life Society, 197385 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 13-15)
  - Life: 1962-1963: Edit: Religion &Science Project, 197384 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Russia Issue, 197383 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Miscellaneous (1), 197382 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 18-19)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Miscellaneous (2), 197381 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Role of Mass Magazine in U.S. by Austell &Grundwald, 197380 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 21-22)
  - Life: 1963 (1964): Edit: Oppenheimer Teller, 197379 (Offsite-box 469, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1963: Publishing, 197378 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Astronauts, 197377 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197376 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Comment, 197375 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (1), 197374 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED], 197373 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (2), 197372 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1964: Publishing, 197371 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Astronauts, 197370 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197369 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Comment, 197368 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Hycon Machine, 197367 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Hycon Machine [RESTRICTED], 197366 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197365 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197364 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1965: Publishing, 197363 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Astronauts, 197362 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197361 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Comment, 197360 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Levi Smith Family Series, 197359 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Photography Issue, 197358 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197357 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197356 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1966: Publishing, 197355 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Astronauts, 197354 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 197353 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Comment, 197352 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Investigative Reporting, 197351 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Investigative Reporting [RESTRICTED], 197350 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197349 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197348 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Publishing, 197347 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Astronauts, 197346 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197345 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Comment, 197344 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (1), 197343 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED], 197342 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Picasso Issue, 197341 (Offsite-box 470, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (2), 197340 (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (2) [RESTRICTED], 197339 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Film Dept., 197338 (Offsite-box 471)
  - Life: 1968: Film Dept. [RESTRICTED], 197337 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Astronauts, 197336 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Comment, 197335 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Comment: Oil Slick, 197334 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Investigative Reporting, 197333 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Supplements (1), 197332 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Supplements (2), 197331 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-May, 197330 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-Dec., 197329 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1969: Film Dept., 197328 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1969: Financial Analyses, 197327 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1969: Publishing, 197326 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 13-14)
  - Life: 1970: Financial Analyses, 197325 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 15-16)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Astronauts, 197324 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Personnel Evaluation, 197323 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Comment: Veteran's Hospitals, 197322 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Comment: Myra Breckenridge, etc, 197321 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Guest Privilege, 197320 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting: Cervantes Article, 197319 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting, 197318 (Offsite-box 471)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting [RESTRICTED], 197317 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Khrushchev Remembers, 197316 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Staff Dinner, 197315 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1970 &Later: Edit: Supplements, 197314 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-May, 197313 (Offsite-box 471, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-Dec., 197312 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 1-2)
  - Life: 1970: Publishing, 197311 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1971 &Later: Edit: Astronauts, 197310 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Comment, 197309 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Comment: Defense Dept. Story, 197308 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Guest Privilege, 197307 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Investigative Reporting, 197306 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 8)
  - Life: 10/8/1971: Edit: Leadership Article, 197305 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Third Century Series, 197304 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1971 7 Later: Edit: Bicentennial Photo Contest, 197303 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197302 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (1), 197301 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (2), 197300 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (3), 197299 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing: Financial Analyses, 197298 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Comment, 197297 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Investigative Reporting, 197296 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197295 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 20-21)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Financial Analyses, 197294 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1972: Edit, 197293 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1972: Publicity about Life's demise, 197292 (Offsite-box 472, Folder 25-26)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-May, 197291 (Offsite-box 472-473)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: June-Sept., 197290 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: June-Sept. [RESTRICTED], 197289 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Oct.-Dec., 197288 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 4-5)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Suspension Announc. Press Conference, 197287 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 6-8)
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Staff Meeting (Tape 2 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Press Conf. (Tape 1 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Press Conf. (Tape 2 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Suspension Announc. Staff Meeting, 197286 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 9)
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Staff Meeting (Tape 1 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
  - Life: 1973, 197285 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1973 [RESTRICTED], 197284 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life Special Report: 1973, 197283 (Offsite-box 473)